This table lists tools used to identify threats that can help to protect
against many types of attacks like virus and malware denial of service attacks.
Spoofing on path and side channel attacks
from monitoring activity on a single computer like
with heads to gathering log data like with seam
to filtering network traffic.
Like with firewalls,
these tools help to protect entire networks and individual systems.
These tools which we will cover more in
depth all help to identify potential threats.
While anti malware firewall and intrusion protection system tools
also have the added ability to prevent threats.